A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.28 (A2002) FA489
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2002.078: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1984-2001; AC.2002.078; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.078.1; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
    - RF 93039 #88 - FARLEY, CARY SCOTT - SSRF: SOIL, CROP, AND PEST MANAGEMENT IN BEAN CROPPING SYSTEMS IN EASTERN AFRICA, 1994-2001 (Box R3495)
    - RF 93039 #89 -MAXWELL, DANIEL GUY - SSRF: FOOD SECURITY AND NUTRITION UNDER URBAN STRESS, 1994-1999 (Box R3495)
    - RF 93039 #90 - WIDAWSKY, DAVID ALAN - SSRF: CROP MANAGEMENT TECHNOLOGY, 1994-2001 (Box R3495)
    - RF 93040 #22 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - INFLUENCE OF LAND USE ON RATES OF DEEP SEEPAGE IN ZIMBABWE, 1993-1999 (Box R3495)
    - RF 93040 #23 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - SOIL MOISTURE CHARACTERISTICS OF ZIMBABWEAN SOIL, 1993-1999 (Box R3495)
    - RF 93043 - PARTNERSHIP FOR CHILD DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1995 (Box R3495)
    - RF 93043 #3 - UNIVERSITY OF OXFORD (ENGLAND) - ANTHELMINTIC AND MICRO-NUTRIENT CHEMOTHERAPY IN CHILDREN, 1993-2001 (Box R3496, Box R3495)
    - RF 93044 - (TRANSFER OF TECHNOLOGY) - TISSUE CULTURE VIRAL VACCINE, 1984-1995 (Box R3497)
    - RF 93044 - (TRANSFER OF TECHNOLOGY) - TISSUE CULTURE VIRAL VACCINE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1984-1995 (Box R3497)
    - RF 93044 #37 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - TECHNOLOGY TRANSFER, 1995-1999 (Box R3497)
    - RF 93045 #3 - PRERANA - ASSOCIATE CENTRE FOR DEVELOPMENT AND POPULATION ACTIVITIES (INDIA) - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH ISSUES AMONG ADOLESCENT GIRLS AND BOYS, 1993-1999 (Box R3497)
    - RF 93046 - COMMONWEALTH REGIONAL HEALTH COMMUNITY SECRETARIAT FOR EAST, CENTRAL AND SOUTHERN AFRICA - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 1988-1998 (Box R3498, Box R3497, Box R3499)
    - RF 93046 - COMMONWEALTH REGIONAL HEALTH COMMUNITY SECRETARIAT FOR EAST, CENTRAL AND SOUTHERN AFRICA - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1988-1998 (Box R3499)
    - RF 93054 - COMPUTER MUSIC RESIDENCIES AND EXCHANGES, 1990-1995 (Box R3499)
    - RF 93055 - COMMUNITY PLANNING AND ACTION - PERSISTENT POVERTY, 1986-1999 (Box R3502, Box R3499, R3500, R3501)
    - RF 93055 - COMMUNITY PLANNING AND ACTION - PERSISTENT POVERTY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1986-1999 (Box R3502, Box R3499, R3500)
- AC.2002.081: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-2002; AC.2002.081; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.081.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE, 1992-2002 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - INSURANCE, 1993-1994 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - LISTS OF JOURNALS/NEWSLETTERS/PEOPLE TO SEND ADVISORIES TO, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZE PANEL, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - NAMES AND CONTACTS, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - RR, 1990-1994 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRESS MATERIAL, 1994 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - FACT SHEETS - "NEED FOR BETTER DIAGNOSTICS", 1994 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - FACT SHEETS - "US", 1994 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - COMPLIANCE - FEDERAL AND STATE LAWS, 1993-1994 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZE RULES - LAWYERS, 1993-1994 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - LAWYERS ADR, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - LAWYERS - PATENTS, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - IRS RULING, 1994 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - IRS RULING REQUEST, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PATENT STUFF, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - CHLAMYDIA TESTS, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - GONORRHEA TESTS, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - LABORATORY VERIFICATION, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - SAMPLE SIZE, 1993-1994 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - INFO/NOTES ON COSTING, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - MANUAL DRAFTS, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - COMMENTS ON DRAFT OF MANUAL BY JUDGING PANELS, 1993-1994 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - BACKGROUND MEETING 1993 JANUARY (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - FINAL COPIES OF THE ADVISORY, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - ADVISORY - RESPONSES - SUBSTANTIVE, 1992-1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - ADVISORY - RESPONSES, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - ADVISORY - PRESS RELEASE, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - COMPUTERS, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - SOLAR AND ELECTRIC CARS, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - MATHEMATICS, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - ASSOCIATION FOR UNMANNED VEHICLE SYSTEMS, 1991 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - AERONAUTICAL, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - MEDICINE - WOOLF, VAN DER VEKEN, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - ENVIRONMENT, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - STUDENT COMPETITIONS - AMERICAN SOCIETY OF MECHANICAL ENGINEERS, undated (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL -STUDENT COMPETITIONS, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - SCIENCE OLYMPIAD, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - STUDENT COMPETITIONS - SOCIETY OF AUTOMOTIVE ENGINEERS, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - EDUCATION, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - REFRIGERATOR CHALLENGE, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - NOBEL PRIZES, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - PAUL MACCREADY, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - 1994 INVENTORS (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - "GRANT MAKING", 1991 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - DANA AWARDS, 1991 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - SCIENCE - AWARDS TO INDIVIDUALS, 1993-1994 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - HISTORICAL - LONGITUDE, undated (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - HISTORICAL - AEROSPACE, undated (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - CLEAN AIR CAR RACE, 1970 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - FEYNMANN, 1991 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - FUNDING SCIENCE, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - HISTORICAL, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - SOLAR INNOVATION AWARD, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZE - BACKGROUND PAPER - SCHRAGE AND KAREL, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - STD PRIZE CORRESPONDENCE - FK, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - CORRESPONDENCE AND MEETINGS, 1992 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - CONTRACEPTION AND OTHER IDEAS, 1993 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - CORRESPONDENCE AND MEETINGS, 1991 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - COMPUTER SEARCH, 1991 (Box R3503)
    - RF 93058 - STD PRIZE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - PRIZES - CONSULTANT'S 1992 REPORT - ARLENE HELLERMAN (Box R3503)
    - RF 93066 #43 - SCIENCE TEACHERS' ASSOCIATION OF MALAWI - SCIENCE AND MATHEMATICS MAGAZINE, 1994-1999 (Box R3504)
    - RF 93066 #46 - SCIENCE CURRICULUM INITIATIVE IN SOUTH AFRICA - SCIENCE LEARNING FOR CHILDREN, 1995-1999 (Box R3504)
    - RF 93066 #52 - SCIENCE TEACHERS ASSOCIATION OF NIGERIA - THE "THINK AND DO" PROJECT, 1993-1997 (Box R3504)
    - RF 93078 #5 - NATIONAL COMMITTEE FOR POPULATION AND FAMILY PLANNING OF VIETNAM - IMPACT OF FAMILY PLANNING AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH SERVICES ON FERTILITY TRANSITION, 1996-1998 (Box R3504)
    - RF 94001 #226 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (NCGEB) (THAILAND) - RICE BLAST POPULATIONS AND DNA FINGERPRINTING, 1993-2000 (Box R3504)
    - RF 94001 #227 - ARMSTRONG, GREGORY - GENETIC ENGINEERING OF PROVITAMIN A BIOSYNTHESIS IN RICE ENDOSPERM, 1993-2000 (Box R3504)
    - RF 94001 #231 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (IRRI) (PHILIPPINES) - MARKER-AIDED SELECTION TECHNIQUES FOR IDENTIFYING FLOOD TOLERANT RICE GENOTYPES, 1993-1998 (Box R3504)
    - RF 94001 #243 - ZHONGSHAN UNIVERSITY - TRANSFORMATION TECHNIQUES FOR RICE IMPROVEMENT, 1990-2001 (Box R3504)
    - RF 94001 #252 - SPIC SCIENCE FOUNDATION - MITOCHONDRIAL GENOM, 1989-2000 (Box R3505)
    - RF 94001 #266 - GUANGDONG ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES (CHINA) - GENES THAT IMPROVE RICE PHOTOSYNTHESIS, YIELD AND QUALITY, 1994-1999 (Box R3505)
    - RF 94001 #277 - ALBERT LUDWIG UNIVERSITY (GERMANY) - FUNCTIONAL EXPRESSION OF CAROTENOGENIC ENZYMES IN RICE ENDOSPERM, 1994-1999 (Box R3505)
    - RF 94001 #278 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE GENETIC IMPROVEMENT, 1993-2000 (Box R3505)
    - RF 94001 #283 - HEALTH RESEARCH INCORPORATED - ROSWELL PARK CANCER INSTITUTE - MAP MANAGER GENETIC MAPPING SOFTWARE, 1992-2000 (Box R3505)
    - RF 94001 #305 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENE RESEARCH - RICE GENOME ANALYSIS, 1994-2000 (Box R3505)
    - RF 94003 #4 - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ORGANIZATION (NARO) (UGANDA) ? PHASE III OF BANANA-BASED CROPPING SYSTEMS PROJECT, 1993-1998 (Box R3505)
    - RF 94004 - MALAWI MAIZE RESEARCH, 1987-1998 (Box R3506)
    - RF 94004 #3 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (DEPT OF) - MAIZE BREEDING PROGRAMS, 1994-1998 (Box R3506)
    - RF 94010 #558 - UNIVERSIDAD IBEROAMERICANA (MEXICO) - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1992-1998 (Box R3506)
    - RF 94017 #4 - ALLIANCE FOR QUALITY EDUCATION - BUILDING AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-2002 (Box R3506)
- AC.2002.086: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-2002; AC.2002.086; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.086.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 94020 #43 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY - RHIZOBIUM ECOLOGY NETWORK OF EAST AND SOUTHERN AFRICA (RENEASA) PROJECT, 1992-2000 (Box R3507)
    - RF 94020 #55 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - SOIL FERTILITY AND CLIMATE IN MAIZE-PRODUCING REGIONS OF KENYA, 1994-1998 (Box R3507)
    - RF 94020 #60 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH PRIORITIES SETTING, 1993-1999 (Box R3507)
    - RF 94022 #1 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE OF INSECT PHYSIOLOGY AND ECOLOGY (KENYA) - IMMUNOLOGICAL INTERACTIONS IN HOST/PARASITOID RELATIONSHIPS, 1994-2001 (Box R3507)
    - RF 94022 #2 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - PROMISCOUS SOYABEAN-RHIZOBIUM SYMBIOSIS AND MAIZE CROPPING, 1994-2001 (Box R3507)
    - RF 94024 #92 - EAST-WEST CENTER - GEOGRAPHICAL MAPPING OF SEX WORKERS IN LAOS, NEPAL AND TAIWAN, 1994-1999 (Box R3507)
    - RF 94025 #14 - UNIVERSITY OF CHILE - TRAINING AND RESEARCH IN FERTILITY REGULATION, 1993-1998 (Box R3507)
    - RF 94025 #22 - INDIAN INSTITUTE OF SCIENCE - FERTILITY REGULATION, 1993-1999 (Box R3507)
    - RF 94027 #577 - GONESE, FRANCIS - ADIA: CONTRIBUTION OF INDIGENOUS FRUIT TREES TO HOUSEHOLD FOOD SECURITY IN ZIMBABWE, 1996-1997 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #581 - MAR GADIO, COUMBA - ADIA: WOMEN'S CHANGING ROLES, ISSUES AND DECISION MAKING, 1995-1998 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #587 - ADUGNA, ABEBE - ADIA: "INTERNATIONAL TRADE AND SMALLHOLDER AGRICULTURE, 1996-1998 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #596 - ABATE, TEFERI - ADIA: "LAND POLICY DISCOURSE AND MICRO-DYNAMICS OF LAND TENURE IN ETHIOPIA", 1996-2000 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #600 - RUGUTT, JOSEPH K. - ACA: "CONTROL OF AFRICAN WITCHWEED BY NATURAL PRODUCTS FROM NATIVE HOSTS AND NON-HOST PLANTS", 1995-2000 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #601 - KEDERA, CHAGEMA JOHN - ACA: "VARIATION AND MYCOTOXIN PRODUCTION BY POPULATIONS OF FUSARIUM PATHOGENS OF MAIZE IN KENYA", 1996-2001 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #606 - HASLER, RICHARD - ACA: COMMUNITY-BASED NATURAL RESOURCE MANAGEMENT, 1996-2001 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #614 - ZAMBERIA, AGOSTINO MATANO - ADIA: WATER AND SANITATION IN KIBERIA, NAIROBI, 1996-1997 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #617 - ADROGU, MICHAEL UGEN - ADIA: ANALYSIS OF COMPETITION AND NUTRIENT MANAGEMENT IN DRY BEAN WEED ASSOCIATION, 1996-1999 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #621 - AHIADEKE, CLEMENT - ACA: HEALTH SEEKING BEHAVIOR OF MOTHERS IN GHANA, 1996-2000 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #622 - MPOFU, BELLAH - ACA: INTEGRATED CONTROL OF WATERHYACINTH IN ZIMBABWE, 1996-1999 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #625 - OLUPOT, WILLIAM - ADIA: "PRIMATE DISPERSAL AND CONSERVATION IN KIBALE NATIONAL PARK, UGANDA", 1996-1999 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #631 - SOGBEDJI, JEAN MIANIKPO - ADIA: NITRATE LEACHING POTENTIAL AND CORN IN SOUTHERN TOGO, 1996-1999 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94027 #633 - IMO, MOSES - ADIA: TREE-CROP INTERACTIONS IN AGROFORESTRY, 1996-1999 (Box R3508)
    - RF 94033 #101 - WINTERS, PAUL CONAL - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURE, 1995-2001 (Box R3509)
    - RF 94033 #102 - MENG, ERIKA CHING-HUEI - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURE, 1995-2000 (Box R3509)
    - RF 94033 #95 - PETERS, DAI HUNG - SSRF: SWEET POTATO RESEARCH, 1994-2001 (Box R3509)
    - RF 94033 #96 - ADATO, MICHELLE - SSRF: EMPLOYMENT CREATION IN SOUTH AFRICA, 1995-2002 (Box R3509)
    - RF 94033 #99 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA) - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP WORKSHOP, 1996-2001 (Box R3509)
    - RF 94038 #12 - ASIA FOUNDATION - INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON SUPPORTING NONPROFIT SECTOR IN ASIA, 1997-2000 (Box R3509)
    - RF 94039 #22 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL OF MUSEUMS (FRANCE) - DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM FOR ARAB-WORLD MUSEUMS, 1993-1999 (Box R3509)
    - RF 94043 #219 - DISTRICT CURATORS - CONTEMPORARY OPERA "THE E+O LINE", 1995-2000 (Box R3509)
    - RF 94050 #6 - UNIVERSIDAD AUTONOMA CHAPINGO - STRENGTHEN ITS CENTER OF AGROFORESTRY FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1998 (Box R3509)
    - RF 94053 #5 - GHANA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - TRACKING INTERNAL MIGRANTS IN NAVRONGO, 1996-1998 (Box R3510)
    - RF 94054 #22 - UNIVERSITY OF COLOMBO (SRI LANKA) - PRE-MARITAL SEXUAL BEHAVIOR AND HIGH INCIDENCE OF ABORTION IN KATUNAYAKE, 1994-2000 (Box R3510)
    - RF 94054 #23 - INSTITUTE FOR EDUCATION AND RESEARCH IN DEMOGRAPHY (CAMEROON) - ADOLESCENT FERTILITY IN CAMEROON, 1995-1998 (Box R3510)
    - RF 94054 #25 - FOUNDATION FOR RESEARCH IN HEALTH SYSTEMS (INDIA) - USE OF REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH SERVICES FOR MARRIED WOMEN UNDER 20 YEARS OF AGE, 1995-1999 (Box R3510)
    - RF 94054 #26 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - FAMILY PLANNING SERVICES FOR WOMENT TREATED FOR ABORTION COMPLICATIONS, 1995-1999 (Box R3510)
    - RF 94055 #15 - SOLAR ELECTRIC LIGHT FUND (SELF) - SOLAR RURAL ELECTRIFICATION IN CHINA, 1992-1997 (Box R3510)
    - RF 94057 #59 - GEOGRAPHY TEACHERS' ASSOCIATION OF MALAWI - ENVIRONMENTAL EDUCATION, 1995-1998 (Box R3510)
    - RF 94057 #66 - NATIONAL MUSEUMS OF KENYA - INTERACTIVE TOYS EXHIBIT, 1996-2000 (Box R3510)
    - RF 94063 #10 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - LABOR FOR LOW-SKILLED YOUNG ADULTS, 1995-1998 (Box R3510)
    - RF 94063 # 9 - W.E. UPJOHN UNEMPLOYMENT TRUSTEE CORPORATION - JOBS FOR THE POOR, 1996-1998 (Box R3510)
    - RF 94069 #61 - CLEVELAND STATE UNIVERSITY - TELECOMMUNICATIONS PROJECT LINKING CLEVELAND STATE UNIVERSITY COLLEGE OF EDUCATION/CLEVELAND PUBLIC SCHOOLS, 1994-2002 (Box R3510)
    - RF 95001 #307 - FUJIAN AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - MAPPING OF QUANTITATIVE TRAIT LOCI (QTLS), 1994-1998 (Box R3510)
    - RF 95001 #308 - FUJIAN AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR RESEARCH ON MAPPING OF QUANTITATIVE TRAIT LOCI (QTLS), 1995-2000 (Box R3510)
- AC.2002.096: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1982-2004; AC.2002.096; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.096.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 94001 #306; RF 95001 #310 - INSTITUTE OF AGRICULTURAL GENETICS (VIETNAM) - MOLECULAR ANALYSIS OF RICE BLAST (PYRICULARIA GRISEA), 1992-1999 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95001 #318 - KANSAS STATE UNIVERSITY - SHEATH BLIGHT PATHOGEN, 1989-1999 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95001 #325 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - POSTDOCTORAL RESEARCH FELLOWS IN RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1994-1998 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95001 #337 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - "MICROSPORE CULTURE IN HYBRID RICE AND WIDE CROSS", 1994-1997 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95001 #342 - AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY INSTITUTE, RURAL DEVELOPMENT ADMINISTRATION (KOREA) - GENETIC MAPPING OF RICE, 1995-1999 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95001 #345 - SHANGHAI INSTITUTE OF PLANT PHYSIOLOGY (CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES) - RICE PATHOGEN RESISTANCE, 1994-1999 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95001 #369 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - MOLECULAR MAPPING ANO RICE BACTERIAL RESISTANCE, 1994-1999 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95001 #370 - CUU LONG DELTA RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (VIETNAM) - ANTHER CULTURE AND RICE IMPROVEMENT IN MEKONG DELTA, 1995-1999 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95001 #373 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1995-1996 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95001 #377 - TAMIL NAOU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (iNDIA) - RHIZOCTONIA TOXIN RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY FELLOWSHIP, 1995-1999 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95002 #477 - UNIVERSIDAD DE LA FRONTERA - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY RESEARCH, 1984-1997 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95002 #479 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT, 1987-1996 (Box R3511)
    - RF 95002 #489 - UNIVERSITY OF RIO DE JANEIRO - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT, 1990-2004 (Box R3512)
    - RF 95002 #491 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY, 1979-1998 (Box R3512)
    - RF 95002 #491 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1979-1998 (Box R3512)
    - RF 95002 #497 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY, 1982-2001 (Box R3512, Box R3513)
    - RF 95002 #497 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1982-2001 (Box R3512, Box R3513)
    - RF 95002 #499 - INCLEN, INC. - XIII GLOBAL MEETING IN ZIMBABWE, 1994-1999 (Box R3513)
    - RF 95005 #78 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - SOIL, CROP AND PEST MANAGEMENT IN EASTERN AFRICA, 1994-2000 (Box R3513)
    - RF 95007 #78 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FACULTY OF AGRICULTURE, 1995-1999 (Box R3513)
    - RF 95008 #20 - TRIOMPHE, BERNARD L. - RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES, 1995-1999 (Box R3513)
    - RF 95010 #44 - FAMILY HEALTH INTERNATIONAL - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH AND FAMILY SERVICES IN GHANA, 1995-1998 (Box R3513)
    - RF 95010 #58 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR DIARRHOEAL DISEASE RESEARCH (BANGLADESH) - AFFECT OF GRAMEEN BANK CREDIT PROGRAM ON FERTILITY, 1995-1998 (Box R3513)
    - RF 95018 #78 - UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL AUTONOMA DE MEXICO - SUSTAINABLE MANAGEMENT OF NATURAL RESOURCES, 1992-1999 (Box R3513)
    - RF 95019 #15 - PURDUE UNIVERSITY - SORGHUM STEM BORER AND ROOT AND STALK ROT RESISTANCE, 1996-1999 (Box R3513)
    - RF 95020 #99 - KENYATTA NATIONAL HOSPITAL - AUTOPSY STUDY IN HIV-1 POSITIVE AND NEGATIVE ACUTE MEDICAL PATIENTS, 1995-1999 (Box R3513)
    - RF 94027 #637; RF 95022 #641 - LAWI, YUSUFU QWARAY - ADIA: FOREST USE ON MBULU PLATEAU, TANZANIA; 1900-1985, 1996-1999 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95020 #102 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - INSTITUTE OF STATISTICS AND APPLIED ECONOMICS - HOUSEHOLD COMPOSITION AND FAMILY STRUCTURE IN THE WAKE OF HIV/AIDS, 1995-1998 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95021 #37; PS 9522 - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH TECHNOLOGIES PROJECT - MICROBICIDES TO PROTECT WOMEN FROM SEXUALLY TRANSMITTED DISEASES, 1995-1999 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95021 #42 - INTERNATIONAL WOMEN'S HEALTH COALITION - SYMPOSIUM ON TESTING OF VAGINAL MICROBICIDES, 1996-2000 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95021 #44 - ALBERT SZENT-GYORGYI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY (HUNGARY) - POSTOVULATORY FERTILITY REGULATING AGENTS, 1995-1999 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95021 #49 - PROGRAM FOR APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY IN HEALTH - PREFERENTIAL PRICING STRUCTURES IN PUBLIC/PRIVATE COLLABORATIONS, 1996-1998 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95022 #639 - EJIKEME, ANENE - ADIA: RELIGION, EDUCATION AND MILITANCY IN ONITSHA, 1996-1999 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95022 #647 - OWUBAH, CHARLES E. - ADIA: STRUCTURE AND PERFORMANCE OF FOREST TENURE IN GHANA, 1997-2002 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95022 #651 - D'SOUZA, ALBA C. - ADIA: FINANCING OF UNIVERSITY EDUCATION IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1997-1999 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95022 #655 - ASSEFA, ZELALEM - ADIA: FAUNAL REMAINS FROM MIDDLE STONE AGE SITES OF ETHIOPIA, 1997-2002 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95022 #657 - NGOM, PIERRE - ACA: COMMUNITY-BASED HEALTH AND FAMILY PLANNING SERVICES EFFECT ON MATERNAL MORTALITY, 1996-2002 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95022 #659 - GORDON, DAVID M. - ADIA: "BIG MEN" OF CENTRAL AFRICA, 1997-2000 (Box R3514)
    - RF 95022 #663 - MWANJA, WILSON WAISWA - ADIA: TILAPIINE AND LABEINE SPECIES OF KYOGA AND VICTORIA LAKE BASINS, 1997-2002 (Box R3514)
- AC.2002.104: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2004; AC.2002.104; 11.79 Cubic Feet 9 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.104.1; 11.79 Cubic Feet 9 record storage boxes
    - RF 95022 #665 - COULIBALY, PAULIN - ADIA: IMPACT OF HUMAN ACTIVITIES ON WATER RESOURCES IN BURKINA FASO, 1996-2000 (Box R3515)
    - RF 95022 #667 - TEMU, ANNA ANDREW - ADIA: AGRICULTURAL COMMODITY MARKETS IN TANZANIA, 1997-1999 (Box R3515)
    - RF 95022 #669 - OSSIYA, SARAH - ADIA: NUTRITIONAL PROFILING SYSTEM FOR FREE-RANGING LIVESTOCK IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1996-1998 (Box R3515)
    - RF 95022 #697 - RAZAFIMANDIMBISON, SYLVAIN - AD/A: SYSTEMATICS AND BIOGEOGRAPHY OF RUBIACEAE-NUCLEAE, 1996-2002 (Box R3515)
    - RF 95022 #701 - KAYA, BOCARY - ADIA: "SOIL FERTILITY REGENERATION THROUGH IMPROVED FALLOW SYSTEMS IN MALI", 1996-1999 (Box R3515)
    - RF 95024 #233 - TRI-CENTRIC FOUNDATION - "COMPOSITION 173", 1995-1998 (Box R3515)
    - RF 95025 #220 - SPIRO, ELLEN - DOCUMENTARY: "THE SLAB CITY SINGLES", 1996-2000 (Box R3515)
    - RF 95025 #235 - TORONTO INTERNATIONAL FILM FESTIVAL (CANADA) - SUBTITLING PROJECT OF "LATIN AMERICAN PANORAMA" PROGRAM, 1995-1998 (Box R3515)
    - RF 95037 #1 - JOHN INNES CENTRE (ENGLAND) - AFRICAN MAIZE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1995-1997 (Box R3515)
    - RF 95038 #100 - OMAMO, STEVEN WERE - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP IN AGRJCULTURE, 1995-1998 (Box R3515)
    - RF 95038 #104 - INTERNATIONAL LIVESTOCK CENTRE FOR AFRICA (ILCA) (ETHIOPIA) - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIP WORKSHOP, 1994-1998 (Box R3515)
    - RF 95039 #38 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - INSTITUTE OF PUBLIC HEALTH - NETWORK OF AFRICAN PUBLIC HEALTH INSTITUTIONS, 1995-1997 (Box R3515)